[
    {
        "front": "的",
        "back": "possessive, adjectival suffix",
        "pronunciation": "de",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "一",
        "back": "one; a, an; alone",
        "pronunciation": "yī",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "是",
        "back": "indeed, yes, right; to be; demonstrative pronoun, this, that",
        "pronunciation": "shì",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "不",
        "back": "no, not; un-; negative prefix",
        "pronunciation": "bù",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "了",
        "back": "to finish; particle of completed action",
        "pronunciation": "le",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "在",
        "back": "be at, in, on; consist in, rest",
        "pronunciation": "zài",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "人",
        "back": "man; people; mankind; someone else",
        "pronunciation": "rén",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "有",
        "back": "have, own, possess; exist",
        "pronunciation": "yǒu",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "我",
        "back": "our, us, i, me, my, we",
        "pronunciation": "wǒ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "他",
        "back": "other, another; he, she, it",
        "pronunciation": "tā",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "这",
        "back": "this, the, here",
        "pronunciation": "zhè",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "个",
        "back": "numerary adjunct, piece; single",
        "pronunciation": "gè",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "们",
        "back": "adjunct pronoun indicate plural",
        "pronunciation": "men",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "中",
        "back": "central; center, middle; in the midst of; hit (target); attain",
        "pronunciation": "zhōng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "来",
        "back": "come, coming; return, returning",
        "pronunciation": "lái",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "上",
        "back": "top; superior, highest; go up, send up",
        "pronunciation": "shàng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "大",
        "back": "big, great, vast, large, high",
        "pronunciation": "dà",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "和",
        "back": "harmony, peace; peaceful, calm",
        "pronunciation": "hé",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "国",
        "back": "nation, country, nation-state",
        "pronunciation": "guó",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "说",
        "back": "speak, say, talk; scold, upbraid",
        "pronunciation": "shuō",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "时",
        "back": "time, season; era, age, period",
        "pronunciation": "shí",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "出",
        "back": "go out, send out; stand; produce",
        "pronunciation": "chū",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "会",
        "back": "assemble, meet together; meeting",
        "pronunciation": "huì",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "你",
        "back": "you, second person pronoun",
        "pronunciation": "nǐ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "对",
        "back": "correct, right; facing, opposed",
        "pronunciation": "duì",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "生",
        "back": "life, living, lifetime; birth",
        "pronunciation": "shēng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "能",
        "back": "to be able; can, permitted to; ability",
        "pronunciation": "néng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "子",
        "back": "offspring, child; fruit, seed of; 1st terrestrial branch",
        "pronunciation": "zi",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "那",
        "back": "that, that one, those",
        "pronunciation": "nà",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "下",
        "back": "under, underneath, below; down; inferior; bring down",
        "pronunciation": "xià",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "年",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "nián",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "后",
        "back": "queen, empress, sovereign; (simp. for後) behind, rear, after",
        "pronunciation": "hòu",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "作",
        "back": "make; work; compose, write; act, perform",
        "pronunciation": "zuò",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "里",
        "back": "unit of distance; village; lane",
        "pronunciation": "lǐ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "家",
        "back": "house, home, residence; family",
        "pronunciation": "jiā",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "多",
        "back": "much, many; more than, over",
        "pronunciation": "duō",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "么",
        "back": "interrogative particle; repetition of a tune small; tender",
        "pronunciation": "me",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "去",
        "back": "go away, leave, depart",
        "pronunciation": "qù",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "学",
        "back": "learning, knowledge; school",
        "pronunciation": "xué",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "都",
        "back": "metropolis, capital; all, the whole; elegant, refined",
        "pronunciation": "dōu",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "同",
        "back": "same, similar; together with",
        "pronunciation": "tóng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "现",
        "back": "appear, manifest, become visible",
        "pronunciation": "xiàn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "没",
        "back": "not, have not, none; drown, sink",
        "pronunciation": "méi",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "面",
        "back": "face; surface; plane; side, dimension",
        "pronunciation": "miàn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "起",
        "back": "rise, stand up; go up; begin",
        "pronunciation": "qǐ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "看",
        "back": "look, see; examine, scrutinize",
        "pronunciation": "kàn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "天",
        "back": "sky, heaven; god, celestial",
        "pronunciation": "tiān",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "分",
        "back": "divide; small unit of time etc.",
        "pronunciation": "fēn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "好",
        "back": "good, excellent, fine; well",
        "pronunciation": "hǎo",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "小",
        "back": "small, tiny, insignificant",
        "pronunciation": "xiǎo",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "些",
        "back": "little, few; rather, somewhat",
        "pronunciation": "xiē",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "样",
        "back": "shape, form, pattern, style",
        "pronunciation": "yàng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "她",
        "back": "she, her",
        "pronunciation": "tā",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "本",
        "back": "root, origin, source; basis",
        "pronunciation": "běn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "前",
        "back": "in front, forward; preceding",
        "pronunciation": "qián",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "开",
        "back": "open; initiate, begin, start",
        "pronunciation": "kāi",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "想",
        "back": "think, speculate, plan, consider",
        "pronunciation": "xiǎng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "机",
        "back": "desk; machine; moment",
        "pronunciation": "jī",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "十",
        "back": "ten, tenth; complete; perfect",
        "pronunciation": "shí",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "工",
        "back": "labor, work; worker, laborer",
        "pronunciation": "gōng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "明",
        "back": "bright, light, brilliant; clear",
        "pronunciation": "míng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "三",
        "back": "three",
        "pronunciation": "sān",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "关",
        "back": "frontier pass; close; relation",
        "pronunciation": "guān",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "点",
        "back": "dot, speck, spot; point, degree",
        "pronunciation": "diǎn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "高",
        "back": "high, tall; lofty, elevated",
        "pronunciation": "gāo",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "很",
        "back": "very, quite, much",
        "pronunciation": "hěn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "见",
        "back": "see, observe, behold; perceive",
        "pronunciation": "jiàn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "什",
        "back": "file of ten soldiers; mixed, miscellaneous",
        "pronunciation": "shén",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "二",
        "back": "two; twice",
        "pronunciation": "èr",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "果",
        "back": "fruit; result",
        "pronunciation": "guǒ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "西",
        "back": "west(ern); westward, occident",
        "pronunciation": "xī",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "月",
        "back": "moon; month; KangXi radical 74",
        "pronunciation": "yuè",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "话",
        "back": "speech, talk, language; dialect",
        "pronunciation": "huà",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "回",
        "back": "return, turn around; a time",
        "pronunciation": "huí",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "老",
        "back": "old, aged; experienced",
        "pronunciation": "lǎo",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "先",
        "back": "first, former, previous",
        "pronunciation": "xiān",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "儿",
        "back": "son, child; KangXi radical 10",
        "pronunciation": "ér",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "东",
        "back": "east, eastern, eastward",
        "pronunciation": "dōng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "水",
        "back": "water, liquid, lotion, juice",
        "pronunciation": "shuǐ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "名",
        "back": "name, rank, title, position",
        "pronunciation": "míng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "几",
        "back": "small table",
        "pronunciation": "jǐ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "认",
        "back": "recognize, know, understand",
        "pronunciation": "rèn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "系",
        "back": "system; line, link, connection",
        "pronunciation": "xì",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "气",
        "back": "steam, vapor; KangXi radical 84",
        "pronunciation": "qì",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "打",
        "back": "strike, hit, beat; fight; attack",
        "pronunciation": "dǎ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "女",
        "back": "woman, girl; feminine; rad. 38",
        "pronunciation": "nǚ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "四",
        "back": "four",
        "pronunciation": "sì",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "电",
        "back": "electricity; electric; lightning",
        "pronunciation": "diàn",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "少",
        "back": "few, less, inadequate",
        "pronunciation": "shǎo",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "太",
        "back": "very, too, much; big; extreme",
        "pronunciation": "tài",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "再",
        "back": "again, twice, re-",
        "pronunciation": "zài",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "做",
        "back": "work, make; act",
        "pronunciation": "zuò",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "期",
        "back": "period of time; date; time limit",
        "pronunciation": "qī",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "五",
        "back": "five; surname",
        "pronunciation": "wǔ",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "书",
        "back": "book, letter, document; writings",
        "pronunciation": "shū",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "听",
        "back": "hear; understand; obey, comply",
        "pronunciation": "tīng",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "住",
        "back": "reside, live at, dwell, lodge; stop",
        "pronunciation": "zhù",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "北",
        "back": "north; northern; northward",
        "pronunciation": "běi",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "觉",
        "back": "to wake up from sleep; conscious",
        "pronunciation": "jué",
        "collection_id": "1"
    },
    {
        "front": "师",
        "back": "teacher, master, specialist",
        "pronunciation": "shī",
        "collection_id": "1"
    }
]